Administrative Files, 1986-1993
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Administrative Files
1986-1993
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Institution, Office of Physical Plant, Horticulture Services Division
SI Records
4 cu. ft. (4 record storage boxes)
Accession 95-131
Descriptive Entry
These records consist of administrative files. The files contain internal and external memorandum and correspondence concerning grounds and greenhouse maintenance, most of which contain horticulture services. There is correspondence from the Blair House, the National Park Service, the Festival of American Folklife, and the Garden Club of America/Archive of American Garden. Additionally there is some correspondence from Environmental Management and Safety deal with hazardous waste disposal and correspondence regarding the United States Soldier and Airmen's Home. Also included are landscape sketches and drawings, vouchers, invoices, and notes for the FY 1990 and 1991.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Blair House (Washington, D.C.); Garden Club of America; United States Soldiers' and Airmen's Home; Smithsonian Institution. Office of Environmental Management and Safety.; Festival of American Folklife
Subject
Hazardous wastes
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts; Drawings
- Box 1
  - 1990 Admin File
  - Incoming (Box 1 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 1 of 4)
  - Outgoing letters (Box 1 of 4)
  - 1990 Budget Allocation (Box 1 of 4)
  - American Association of Botanical Gardens and Arboreta (AABGA) (Box 1 of 4)
  - 2R Account (Box 1 of 4)
  - AI Balcony (Box 1 of 4)
  - Accountable Mail (Box 1 of 4)
  - Activities and management report (Box 1 of 4)
  - Adler Display (Box 1 of 4)
  - Agreements for loans or exhibitions (Box 1 of 4)
  - Agreement for outgoing loan (Box 1 of 4)
  - Airborne Express (Box 1 of 4)
  - Allocation Reappraisal (Box 1 of 4)
  - Alviti, John (Box 1 of 4)
  - American Airlines (Box 1 of 4)
  - American Horticultural Society (Box 1 of 4)
  - American Society (Box 1 of 4)
  - Annual Report (Box 1 of 4)
  - Appraisal (Box 1 of 4)
  - Appreciation (Box 1 of 4)
  - Armstrong, Anne (Box 1 of 4)
  - ATI (Box 1 of 4)
  - Blackburn, Sadie Gwinn (Box 1 of 4)
  - Blair, Dubilier and Associates (Box 1 of 4)
  - Blair House Restoration Fund (Box 1 of 4)
  - Block, Carolyn (Box 1 of 4)
  - Brusch, Larry (Box 1 of 4)
  - Buckler, Jim (Box 1 of 4)
  - Call for Plans, FY 1991 thru 1997 (Box 1 of 4)
  - Canterbury International (Box 1 of 4)
  - CASD Meeting (Box 1 of 4)
  - Chicago Botanic Garden (Box 1 of 4)
  - Connecticut Historical Society (Box 1 of 4)
  - Construction pedestrian directional signage (Box 1 of 4)
  - Cunningham, Carter (Box 1 of 4)
  - Curry, Robert (Box 1 of 4)
  - Deed of Gift (Box 1 of 4)
  - Diversity (Box 1 of 4)
  - Draft 5-Year prospectus, FY 1991-1995 (Box 1 of 4)
  - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 1 of 4)
  - Folger Urn Collection (Box 1 of 4)
  - Furloughs (Box 1 of 4)
  - FY 1992 Budget Submission Phase I and II (Box 1 of 4)
  - GL Cornell Company (Box 1 of 4)
  - Garden Source (Box 1 of 4)
  - Garden Source Furnishings (Box 1 of 4)
  - Green Meadows, Inc. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Grants (Box 1 of 4)
  - Hanes, John W., Jr. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Hen Feathers (Box 1 of 4)
  - Hider, Rick (Box 1 of 4)
  - Hospital for Sick Children (Box 1 of 4)
  - Horticultural Services Division (HAD) Party (Box 1 of 4)
  - Image Management Corp (Box 1 of 4)
  - Impact Statement of FY 1990 Budget Cuts (Box 1 of 4)
  - Invitation/Reception (Box 1 of 4)
  - Iron Works (Box 1 of 4)
  - James Smithson (Box 1 of 4)
  - Jim's Scrapbook (Box 1 of 4)
  - Journal of Garden History (Box 1 of 4)
  - Leinbachs, Inc. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Lewis, Hewett W. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Loan of Government Owned Property (Box 1 of 4)
  - Margaret Woodbury Strong Museum (Box 1 of 4)
  - Mary Livingston Ripley Garden (Box 1 of 4)
  - New Arrivals (Box 1 of 4)
  - Northern Virginia Nurserymen's Association (Box 1 of 4)
  - Oglebay Institute (Box 1 of 4)
  - Organization Charts (HSD) (Box 1 of 4)
  - Potomac Industrial Trucks Inc. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Professional Shoe Service (Safety boots0 (Box 1 of 4)
  - Program Report (Box 1 of 4)
  - Ripley, Mrs. S. Dillon (Box 1 of 4)
  - Shuttle and mail service (Box 1 of 4)
  - SI 1990 Collection Statistics and Highlights (Box 1 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Council Report 1990 Meeting (Box 1 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Museum Accreditation (Box 1 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Year FY 1990 (Box 1 of 4)
  - Staff meeting agenda (Box 1 of 4)
  - Sunny O'Neil (Box 1 of 4)
  - Thank you folder (Box 1 of 4)
  - Training (Box 1 of 4)
  - Uncle Beasley (Box 1 of 4)
  - University of South Carolina (Box 1 of 4)
  - Use of the garden (Box 1 of 4)
  - Use of power lifts and reinstallation of Folger Collection Urns (Box 1 of 4)
  - Valentiner Benedicte (Box 1 of 4)
  - Victorian Gardens Order (Box 1 of 4)
  - Visitor comments (3 folders) (Box 1 of 4)
  - Wanderman, Lisa (Box 1 of 4)
  - Wetsel Seed Company (Box 1 of 4)
  - Willow Run Company, Inc. (Box 1 of 4)
  - Yoder Brothers, Inc. (Box 1 of 4)
  - 1990 Grounds Management File
  - Incoming (Box 1 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 1 of 4)
  - Activation of Water and Sprinkler System (Box 1 of 4)
  - Containers (Box 1 of 4)
  - Dinosaur (Box 1 of 4)
  - Enid A. Haupt Garden (Box 1 of 4)
  - Hypodermic needles (Box 1 of 4)
  - Infant center play area (Box 1 of 4)
  - Integrated pest management (Box 1 of 4)
  - Moving plant materials in Ripley Garden (Box 1 of 4)
  - Pest control (Box 1 of 4)
  - Snow and ice removal plan (Box 1 of 4)
  - Space for GMB/Office of Horticulture (OH) update (Box 1 of 4)
  - 1990 Greenhouse File
  - Incoming (Box 1 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 1 of 4)
  - A Campaign to Remember (Box 1 of 4)
  - Agreement between OH and MSL of the Greenhouse/Nursery Division (GND) (Box 1 of 4)
  - Display labels for spring tulips (Box 1 of 4)
  - FY annual orders proposal (Box 1 of 4)
  - GND safety meeting (Box 1 of 4)
- Box 2
  - Greenhouse/Nursery Division Disaster Preparedness Plan (Box 2 of 4)
  - Letters of GND tour requests (Box 2 of 4)
  - Orchid show and collections (Box 2 of 4)
  - Plant list for spring planting (Box 2 of 4)
  - Plants rented from outside vendor and supplemented from OH/GND (Box 2 of 4)
  - Special events (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Interior File (Plant Division)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Enid Haupt Garden tour request incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Enid Haupt Garden tour request outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Haupt Garden Information for exhibitions, Directory and Calendar of Events (Box 2 of 4)
  - Holiday decorations (Box 2 of 4)
  - Museum cafeteria interior plant program (Box 2 of 4)
  - Records, labeling, and accessions training materials program (Box 2 of 4)
  - Reproduction terms and fees (Box 2 of 4)
  - Rotational plants (Box 2 of 4)
  - Special events (Box 2 of 4)
  - Statistics for annual report (Box 2 of 4)
  - Trees of Christmas incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Trees of Christmas outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Trees of Christmas loan policy (Box 2 of 4)
  - Women's committee ball (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 GCA/AAG (Garden Club of America/Archive of American Gardens)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Blackburn, Sadie Gwinn (Box 2 of 4)
  - AAG policy and procedures (Box 2 of 4)
  - AAG processing procedures and personnel (Box 2 of 4)
  - Bissell, Gina (Box 2 of 4)
  - Database materials (Box 2 of 4)
  - Fisher, Laura (Box 2 of 4)
  - GCA/AAG minutes (Box 2 of 4)
  - Jones, Gloria (Box 2 of 4)
  - Mary Livingston Ripley Garden (MLRG) Dedication (Box 2 of 4)
  - Practical use of the AAG (Box 2 of 4)
  - Procedure for handling slides (Box 2 of 4)
  - Project manager, AAG (Box 2 of 4)
  - Receiving reports (Box 2 of 4)
  - Robinson, Betty (Box 2 of 4)
  - Rollins, Helen (Box 2 of 4)
  - Titus, Joanne (Box 2 of 4)
  - Weller, Eleanor (Box 2 of 4)
  - West, Millicent (Box 2 of 4)
  - Yellott, Sandy (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Women's Committee
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Computerized engraving machine (Box 2 of 4)
  - Women's Committee membership list (Box 2 of 4)
  - Women's Committee Project Awards (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Festival of American Folklife
  - Letter - Doris Dietrich (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Accounting and Finance
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Establishment of new fund numbers and organization code (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Procurement and Property Management (OPPM)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Procurement management review of the Office of Horticulture (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Environmental Management and Safety (OEMS)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Discharges to the wastewater system (Box 2 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste coordinator meeting (Box 2 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste disposal program (Box 2 of 4)
  - NASM internal safety and fire protection (Box 2 of 4)
  - Pesticide (Box 2 of 4)
  - Safety coordinator's meeting (Box 2 of 4)
  - Safety and occupational health survey (Box 2 of 4)
  - SI Disaster Preparedness Procedures (Box 2 of 4)
  - SI Hazardous Chemicals Emergency Spill and Leak Control Procedures (Box 2 of 4)
  - SI Statistical Report Program Activities (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Planning and Budget (OPB)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - 3 Quarter FY 1990 trust fund projections (Box 2 of 4)
  - Congressional appropriations hearing (Box 2 of 4)
  - FY 1991 federal salaries and expenses (Box 2 of 4)
  - Justification for FY 1991 budget submission (Box 2 of 4)
  - Permission to exceed FTE allocation in FY 1991 and FY 1992 (Box 2 of 4)
  - Reprogramming other objects surplus (Box 2 of 4)
  - Justification for the FY 1992 budget submission (Box 2 of 4)
  - FY 1992 budget (Box 2 of 4)
  - FY 1991 budget allocation (Box 2 of 4)
  - Budget (trust) (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Design and Construction (ODC)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Proposed FY 1992 RR and AM program for the Office of Horticulture (Box 2 of 4)
  - 883417 - Exterior perimeter, courtyard and fence repairs (NMAA) (Box 2 of 4)
  - 883501 - NASM - Miscellaneous HVAC projects (Box 2 of 4)
  - 900007 - Consolidation of Grounds Management Division space (Box 2 of 4)
  - 906309 - Path accessibility and south tower exterior accessibility (Box 2 of 4)
  - 906310 - Quadrangle leaks study (Box 2 of 4)
  - 8632107W - Window restoration - Phases II and III (SIB) (Box 2 of 4)
  - 8637104 - Additions and alterations (FGA) (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Fellowships and Grants
  - Stipend awards (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Office of Registrar
  - Collaborations (Box 2 of 4)
  - Registrar deadline (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Resident Associate Program (RAP)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Experimental Gallery
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Anacostia Museum
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Anacostia Museum landscaping (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 National Park Service
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 National Air and Space Museum (NASM)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 2 of 4)
  - Meeting (Box 2 of 4)
  - Response to NASM interior safety and fire protection review (Box 2 of 4)
  - Response to safety and fire protection review NASM (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 National Zoological Park (NZP)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - 1990 Office of Protection Services (OPS)
  - Incoming (Box 2 of 4)
  - Update emergency notification list (Box 2 of 4)
  - USSAH (United States Solider and Airmen's Home)
  - Agreements (Box 2 of 4)
  - Greenhouse Nursery Division (Box 2 of 4)
  - MSL (Marine Systems Laboratory) (Box 2 of 4)
  - Correspondence (Box 2 of 4)
  - Proposed Greenhouse Nursery Operation (miscellaneous information) (Box 2 of 4)
  - Blair House
  - Correspondence (Box 2 of 4)
  - Budget
  - FY 1986 Trust, FY 1987 Federal, FY 1987-1991 Five Year Prospectus (submission) (3 folders) (Box 2 of 4)
- Box 3
  - FY 1987 Trust, FY 1988 Federal, FY 1988-1992 Five Year Prospectus (submission) (4 folders; Folder 1 contains 5.25" floppy disk) (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Admin File
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 3 of 4)
  - Incoming letters (Box 3 of 4)
  - Outgoing letters (Box 3 of 4)
  - AABGS (American Association of Botanical Gardens and Arboreta) (Box 3 of 4)
  - ABC Guide to Gardens, Arboreta and Nurseries (Box 3 of 4)
  - Acquisitions funding for the library (Box 3 of 4)
  - Acting director for HSD (Box 3 of 4)
  - Activities and management report (Box 3 of 4)
  - Administrative procedures (Box 3 of 4)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA) (Box 3 of 4)
  - Appointment of accessibility liaisons and alternates (Box 3 of 4)
  - Audio-visual services for horticulture workshop (Box 3 of 4)
  - Ball State University (Box 3 of 4)
  - Boese, Carl (Box 3 of 4)
  - Botany Department (Box 3 of 4)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Bulb order for 1991 planting (Box 3 of 4)
  - Call for plans (Box 3 of 4)
  - Career service emblems (Box 3 of 4)
  - CASD meeting (Council of Administrative and Service Directors) (Box 3 of 4)
  - Care Award (Box 3 of 4)
  - Catering (Box 3 of 4)
  - Cheekwood (Box 3 of 4)
  - Collections Management Policies (Box 3 of 4)
  - Connelly, John (Box 3 of 4)
  - Curry, Robert (Box 3 of 4)
  - Cushwa Brick Inc. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Detail of FY 1990 Base Analysis Data (Box 3 of 4)
  - Diane Genre Oriental Art and Antiquities, Inc. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 3 of 4)
  - Engraving machine (Box 3 of 4)
  - ERIE Insurance Group (Box 3 of 4)
  - Essential employees (Box 3 of 4)
  - Explus Inc. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Federal Yellow Book (Box 3 of 4)
  - Federated Garden Clubs of Maryland, Inc. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Fiberglass urn liners (Box 3 of 4)
  - Fiberglass urns reimbursement (Box 3 of 4)
  - Floriade (Box 3 of 4)
  - Flowers Magazine (Box 3 of 4)
  - Folger, Lee M. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Fred C. Gloeckner Foundation Annual Report (Box 3 of 4)
  - Friends of Bugs (Box 3 of 4)
  - FY 1991 Trust Fund Budget Shortfall (Box 3 of 4)
  - Gardens and countrysides (Box 3 of 4)
  - Garden Club of America (GCA) Zone meeting (Box 3 of 4)
  - Greenhorne O'Mara, Inc. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Gichner - JMB (Box 3 of 4)
  - Gift list review (Box 3 of 4)
  - Haupt, Enid A. (Box 3 of 4)
  - Honorable John Warner (Box 3 of 4)
  - Horticulture Chronology (Box 3 of 4)
  - HSD goals and objectives FY 1992 (Box 3 of 4)
  - HSD Situation Analysis (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Festival of American Folklife
  - Outgoing (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Product Development and Licensing (OPDL)
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Gardener's Journal (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Fellowships and Grants
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Office of Registrar (OR)
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - Collection statistics, 1991 (Box 3 of 4)
  - Meeting (Box 3 of 4)
  - Project success (Box 3 of 4)
  - Project success through problem solving (Box 3 of 4)
  - SI Registrars survey (Box 3 of 4)
  - Transportation services (Box 3 of 4)
  - Water detectors (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Office of Risk Management
  - Monthly register (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Experimental Gallery
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Anacostia Museum
  - Horticulture upgrade for Anacostia Museum (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 National Park Service
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 NASM
  - Outgoing (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Arthur M. Sackler Gallery
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Women's Committee
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - Silent auction contract (Box 3 of 4)
  - Women's Committee members (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Office of Plant Services (OPlantS)
  - Incoming (Box 3 of 4)
  - Detail of federal funding (Box 3 of 4)
  - Manual of OPlantS Policy and Procedure (Box 3 of 4)
  - Meetings (Box 3 of 4)
  - Open audit recommendations (Box 3 of 4)
  - OPlantS service manual (Box 3 of 4)
  - Program of requirements (Box 3 of 4)
  - Proposed transfer of OH to OPlantS (Box 3 of 4)
  - Safety meeting (Box 3 of 4)
  - Workhour allocation (Box 3 of 4)
  - Work schedule on form 23 (Box 3 of 4)
  - GCA (Box 3 of 4)
  - Professional Grounds Management Society (Box 3 of 4)
  - National Institute on Park and Grounds Management (Box 3 of 4)
  - AABGA (Box 3 of 4)
  - Professional organizations (Box 3 of 4)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 3 of 4)
  - 1991 Grounds Management File
  - Incoming outgoing (Box 3 of 4)
  - Activation of water and sprinkler system (Box 3 of 4)
  - Dinosaur (Box 3 of 4)
  - Enid Haupt Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - GMB storage areas (Box 3 of 4)
  - Grounds safety meeting (Box 3 of 4)
  - Infant center play area (Box 3 of 4)
  - Landscapes and ground for historic building (Box 3 of 4)
  - Lighting in Haupt Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Location of sculptures in the garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Mary Livingston Ripley Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Project in the Hirshhorn Sculpture Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Snow and ice removal plan (Box 3 of 4)
  - Space for GMB/OH update (Box 3 of 4)
  - Trees in Haupt Garden (Box 3 of 4)
  - Tree spraying (Box 3 of 4)
  - Watering the Haupt Garden (Box 3 of 4)
- Box 4
  - 1991 Greenhouse File
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - GND safety meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - Greenhouse tour schedule (Box 4 of 4)
  - Letters of GND tour request (Box 4 of 4)
  - Integrated pest management in the Cowles Conservatory (Box 4 of 4)
  - Orchid Show and Collections (Box 4 of 4)
  - Pesticide (Box 4 of 4)
  - Renwick Gallery (Box 4 of 4)
  - Shaffer, John (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 GCA/AAG
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - Buckler, Jim (Box 4 of 4)
  - Database materials (Box 4 of 4)
  - Deed of gift (Box 4 of 4)
  - Delivery of the database (Box 4 of 4)
  - Frinier, Richard (Box 4 of 4)
  - GCA/AAG agenda (Box 4 of 4)
  - GCA/AAG minutes (Box 4 of 4)
  - Wave Hill (Box 4 of 4)
  - Weller, Eleanor (Box 4 of 4)
  - West, Millicent (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 Building Management
  - Annual report of Safety Activities (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 General (Admin)
  - James Posey Associates (Box 4 of 4)
  - James Smithson (Box 4 of 4)
  - Landscape Architecture, Planning, Historic Preservation (Box 4 of 4)
  - Lecture (Box 4 of 4)
  - Lewis, Hewett (Box 4 of 4)
  - List of email subscribers (Box 4 of 4)
  - Longwood Gardens (Box 4 of 4)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens (Box 4 of 4)
  - Memo of Agreement of Transfer of the OH (Box 4 of 4)
  - Monthly reports (Box 4 of 4)
  - Moscow exhibits (Box 4 of 4)
  - Museum and Library of Maryland History (Box 4 of 4)
  - National Capital Orchid Society (Box 4 of 4)
  - OASM staff meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - Objectives for organization study and resulting management improvement plan (Box 4 of 4)
  - Office of Communication (Box 4 of 4)
  - Oglebay Institute (Box 4 of 4)
  - Organic Garden Committee Members minutes (Box 4 of 4)
  - Poor III, Edward King (Box 4 of 4)
  - Poulin-Deltour (Box 4 of 4)
  - Program report (Box 4 of 4)
  - Public inquiry mail service (Box 4 of 4)
  - Reid, Zak (Box 4 of 4)
  - Return materials (Box 4 of 4)
  - Reorganization of the OH (Box 4 of 4)
  - Ripley, S. Dillon (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety survey (Box 4 of 4)
  - Security of 2282 AI OH (Box 4 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Libraries (Box 4 of 4)
  - Smithsonian Year FY 1991 (Box 4 of 4)
  - Special Exhibition Fund (Box 4 of 4)
  - Staff meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - Stolen works of art - Canada (Box 4 of 4)
  - Streeter, Richard H. (Box 4 of 4)
  - Sunshine Farm and Gardens (Box 4 of 4)
  - TDY Reports (Box 4 of 4)
  - Thank you folder (Box 4 of 4)
  - National Arbor Day Foundation (Box 4 of 4)
  - The Scott Arboretum of Swarthmore (Box 4 of 4)
  - Tour of gardens with interns (Box 4 of 4)
  - Training (Box 4 of 4)
  - Truppi, Carol (Box 4 of 4)
  - Update emergency notification list (Box 4 of 4)
  - Update on OH (Box 4 of 4)
  - Use of the garden (Box 4 of 4)
  - Victorian Gardens booklets (Box 4 of 4)
  - Victorian Gardens order (Box 4 of 4)
  - Victorian Garden show (Box 4 of 4)
  - Video release form (Box 4 of 4)
  - Visitor comment (Box 4 of 4)
  - Volunteer program (Box 4 of 4)
  - Wanderman, Lisa (Box 4 of 4)
  - Waterford gardens (Box 4 of 4)
  - Wetsel Seed Company, Inc. (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 Interior File
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - Docent training handbook (Box 4 of 4)
  - Enid Haupt Garden tour request incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Enid Haupt Garden tour request outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - Flowers in SDR concourse (Box 4 of 4)
  - Haupt Garden information for exhibitions, directory and calendar of events (Box 4 of 4)
  - Holiday exhibition (Box 4 of 4)
  - Internship (Box 4 of 4)
  - Special events Haupt Garden (Box 4 of 4)
  - Trees of Christmas incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Trees of Christmas outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 Procurement and Property Management (OPPM)
  - Procurement management review of the Office of Horticulture (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 Environmental Management and Safety (OEMS)
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Annual report of safety activities for FY 1991 (Box 4 of 4)
  - Asbestos Management Plan and Operations and Maintenance Program (Box 4 of 4)
  - Follow-up response for survey findings (Box 4 of 4)
  - FY 1993 Budget for health / safety (Box 4 of 4)
  - Hazardous chemicals emergency spill and leak control (Box 4 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste coordinators' meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste disposal program (Box 4 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste report for 1990 (Box 4 of 4)
  - Hazardous waste (Box 4 of 4)
  - Management Evaluation and Technical review of the National Museum of American History (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety and Occupational Health Survey of the GND/OH (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety coordinators' meeting (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety and health program (Box 4 of 4)
  - Safety report (Box 4 of 4)
  - SI Statistical Report of Safety Program (Box 4 of 4)
  - Waste minimization guidance (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 Planning and Budget (OPB)
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - 1991 design and Construction (ODC)
  - Incoming (Box 4 of 4)
  - Outgoing (Box 4 of 4)
  - Project activity report (Box 4 of 4)
  - 86307 - Quadrangle Design and Construction items (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8245104 - HMSG plaza renovation and landscape (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8338104 - Suitland Collections Research Center Master plan (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8632107W - Window restoration phases II and III (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8637102 - FGA - Gallery renovation (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8637104 - FGA - Additions and alterations (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8748105 - Cooper-Hewitt - Accessibility implementation, Phase II (Box 4 of 4)
  - 8770101 - SI-Wide facilities inventory and strategic plan, Phase I (Box 4 of 4)
  - 883417 - AAPG - exterior perimeter, courtyard and fence repairs (Box 4 of 4)
  - 897001 - Mall master plan for site improvements (Box 4 of 4)
  - 900007 - Consolidation of Ground Management Division office space (Box 4 of 4)
  - 903504 - NASM handicap accessibility improvements (Box 4 of 4)
  - 903506 - NASM handicap accessibility improvements (Box 4 of 4)
  - 903701 - FGA auditorium renovation (Box 4 of 4)
  - 906309 - Mary Livingston Ripley Garden - Existing lamppost anchor bolts (Box 4 of 4)
  - 906310 - Quadrangle building leak problems (Box 4 of 4)
  - 913130 - NMNH - Uncle Beasley relocation (Box 4 of 4)
  - 914408 - Visitor's Center roof replacement (Box 4 of 4)
  - 914409 - Visitor's Center roof replacement (Box 4 of 4)
  - 914503 - HMSG - Miscellaneous HVAC repairs (Box 4 of 4)
  - 914513 - HMSG - Conference room conversion (Box 4 of 4)
  - 916308 - Infant care center outdoor activity area location (Box 4 of 4)
  - 926305 - Quad - Views of Paradise (Box 4 of 4)
  - Budget
  - FY 1988 Trust, FY 1989 Federal, FY 19089-1993 Five Year Prospectus (submission) (1 of 2) (Box 4 of 4)
  - FY 1988 Trust, FY 1989 Federal, FY 19089-1993 Five Year Prospectus (submission) (2 of 2) (Box 4 of 4)